{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which animation studio produced &quot;Log Horizon&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Satelite",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sunrise",
        "Xebec",
        "Production I.G"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Medaka Kurokami from &quot;Medaka Box&quot; has what abnormality?",
      "correct_answer": "The End",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Perfection",
        "Sandbox",
        "Fairness"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which animation studio produced the anime adaptation of &quot;xxxHolic&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Production I.G",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sunrise",
        "Xebec",
        "Kyoto Animation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Uzumaki?",
      "correct_answer": "Junji Ito",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "\tNoboru Takahashi",
        "Akira Toriyama",
        "Masashi Kishimoto"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which animation studio animated &quot;Psycho Pass&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Production I.G",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Kyoto Animation",
        "Shaft",
        "Trigger"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In what year did the manga &quot;Ping Pong&quot; begin serialization?",
      "correct_answer": "1996",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2014",
        "2010",
        "2003"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "What year was &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood&quot; first released?",
      "correct_answer": "1987",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2013",
        "1983",
        "1995"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Akatsuki&#039;s subclass in &quot;Log Horizon&quot; is what?",
      "correct_answer": " Tracker",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Assassin",
        "Scribe",
        "Apprentice"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which animation studio animated &quot;To Love-Ru&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Xebec",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trigger",
        "Sunrise",
        "Kyoto Animation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Who is One Punch Man voiced by in the Japanese version.",
      "correct_answer": "Makoto Furukawa",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Zach Aguilar",
        "Kaito Ishikawa",
        "Max Mittelman "
      ]
    }
  ]
}